Python for Quest library makes HTTP requests easy.
Python Quest 库令 HTTP 请求变得简单
It has a method called get which will send the request for us,
它有一种名为 get 的方法 将为我们发送请求
return the contents of the file we requested, which for us,
返回我们请求的文件的内容 对我们而言
is a text file, which we can then save to a file.
它是一个文本文件 我们可以保存至文件中
This is how we programmatically download a file from the Internet.
这是我们通过编程从互联网下载文件的方式
Here's how it's done. It's super simple.
这就是操作方法 超级简单
We import the request library,
我们导入请求库
and we'll actually import the OS library,
我们实际上导入的是 OS 库
too, so we can store the downloaded file in a folder called ebert_reviews.
所以 我们可以将下载的文件存储至 名为 ebert_reviews 的文件夹中
This bit of code here just creates the folder ebert_reviews if it doesn't exist already.
如果尚不存在 这部分代码会创建文件夹 ebert_reviews
Here comes the actual bit of request code.
这是实际的请求代码
We use requests.get on a URL,
我们在 URL 上使用 requests.get
and that returns a response.
然后返回一个响应
And I'll give you this you this URL here.
在这里 我会给你这个 URL
Here is the URL for the Roger Ebert reviews
这是 Roger Ebert 影评文本文件的 URL
text file that I saved on new Udacity's servers.
我已保存在新的 Udacity 的服务器上
So we haven't actually saved the response to anything yet,
所以 实际上 我们并未将响应保存至任何文件夹中
but let's take a look at what this response variable looks like.
但我们来看看这个响应变量的样子
And we see response 200.
我们看看响应 200
200 being the HTTP status code for the request has succeeded.
200 表示请求的 HTTP 状态代码 已成功
So that's good. So this response returned from the requests.get method.
所以 很好 这就是 request.get 法返回的响应
You can't see it currently,
你目前还看不到它
but all the text in our text file is actually in
但我们文本文件中的所有文本实际上
our computer's working memory right now within this response variable.
还在我们计算机的工作记忆中 目前在这个响应变量内
It's stored in the body of the response which we can access using.content,
它存储在响应主体中 我们可以用 .content 访问它
as shown in the request library documentation. Let's check it out.
如请求库文档中所示 我们来一探究竟
And okay, there it all is.
好的 这就是全部操作
It's in bytes format.
它采用字节格式
Using this and some basic file IO,
使用这个基本文件 IO
we're going to save this file to our computer.
我们把这个文件保存至计算机中
So we'll open a file called 11-e.t-the-extra-terrestrial.txt, i.e.
这样我们将打开一个名为 11-e.t-the-extra-terrestrial.txt 的文件 即
everything after the last slash in this URL.
这个 URL 中最后一个斜线后的所有内容
And to get everything after that last slash,
要想获得最后一个斜线后的所有内容
we'll use Python's split function,
我们将使用 Python 的 split 函数
and select the last item in the list returned.
然后选择所返回名单中的最后一个项目
And we need to open this file which
我们需要打开这个文件
will then write the contents of the response variable to.
接着将把响应变量的内容写入至该文件中
We have to open this in WB mode, Write Binary.
我们必须在 WB 即 Write Binary 模式下打开这个文件
That's because response.content is in bytes and not text. But don't worry.
这是因为 response.content 是字节格式 而不是文本格式 但请不要担心
When we open these files in a text editor or in Pandas later,
当我们稍后在 文本编辑器 或 Pandas 中打开这些文件时
the bytes will be rendered as human readable text.
字节将渲染为人类可读文本
Then we write to the file handle we've opened, file.write response.
接着 我们写入至我们已打开的文件句柄中 即 file.write response.content
content. And that should do it.
这样就行了
That's how you download one file programmatically.
这就是如何通过编程下载一个文件的方法
Let's check the contents of our folder ebert_reviews
我们来查看一下我们文件夹 ebert_reviews 的内容
to make sure this worked. And there it is.
以保证这种方法有效 就是这样
This.DS_Store is a hidden file that
这个 .DS_Store 是一个隐藏文件
stores the attributes of our folder. Ignore that for now.
它存储了我们文件夹的属性 请暂时忽略这一点
And if you go to your Jupyter Notebook dashboard,
如果你转至 Jupyter Notebook 控制面板
and open that file,
然后打开这个文件
you'll see that the entirety of it was correctly downloaded.
你就会发现整个文件已正确下载
So again, that's how you download one file.
再说一下 这就是如何下载一个文件的方法
But if we have lots of files to download though,
但如果我们有许多文件要下载
like we do for all of these Ebert reviews for the top 100 Rotten Tomatoes movie list,
就像我们针对烂番茄百佳影片的全部 Ebert 影评所做的事情一样
writing a lot of these statements would be annoying.
那么写许多这样的语句 就会让人恼火
Luckily, downloading files programmatically scales well.
幸运的是 也可以通过编程下载文件
You can use a for loop over all of the file URLs to minimize code repetition.
你可以对所有文件 URL 使用 for 循环 以减少代码重复
Lucky for you, I've provided the URLs for you here.
你们很幸运 在这里 我已经为你们提供了 URL
Your task now is to write this loop,
你们现在的任务就是写这个循环
and download all of the Roger Ebert review files programmatically.
然后通过编程下载所有的 Roger Ebert 影评文件